conexis.com 2014-04-05

# Privacy Policy | CONEXIS

### CONEXIS Website Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the CONEXIS Benefits Administrators, LP (“CONEXIS”) website. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, CONEXIS is providing this policy to explain the online information policies and practices CONEXIS maintains concerning the privacy of users’ information at the CONEXIS website (“Site”). By browsing this Site and sending information to CONEXIS, you are consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

In this policy, the terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to CONEXIS and “you” refers to the individual using the Site.

**Effective Date of this Privacy Policy: This Privacy Policy is effective January 16, 2012.**

### The Information We Collect

CONEXIS will receive and store personally identifiable information about you whenever you provide this information to us through this Site. We may also obtain personally identifiable information about you from third parties. This can happen in several ways. We may obtain information about employers and their employees through a participating insurance broker. This can occur when the employer requests a quote for COBRA administration services. In order to obtain a quote from CONEXIS, the broker will obtain information regarding the employer’s business and employees and provide this information to us. We may also receive information regarding employers and employees when a broker manages his/her account, among other things. We may also receive information from carriers and third party administrators when they submit information to CONEXIS.

The information we receive may vary by product; therefore, the examples that follow may not apply to all customers but are designed to show the general categories of information that may be received and maintained by CONEXIS:

• Information provided by you on applications, forms, surveys and our Websites, such as:

  * your name,
  * address,
  * date of birth,
  * Social Security Number,
  * gender,
  * marital status, and/or,
  * dependents

• Information provided by your employer; 

• Information about your transactions and experiences with CONEXIS such as:

  * products or services purchased,
  * account balances,
  * payment history,
  * policy coverage, and/or
  * premiums

### Cookies and Log Files

This Site uses a standard technology called ‘cookies’, which collects information about a user’s session. . A cookie is a small file created by an Internet site to store information on your computer. Cookies do not allow websites to gain access to other information on your computer. Once a cookie is saved on your computer, only the website that created the cookie can read it. We also record the IP or Internet Protocol address of users who log on to our Site for additional security tracking purposes.

### How We Use the Information We Collect

We may disclose the personal information (not your personal health information) we receive, as described above, to the following types of third parties:

• Other third parties as permitted or required by law, such as:

  * for compliance with a subpoena,
  * fraud prevention, or 
  * inquiries from state or federal regulatory agencies

• Financial service companies with whom we have agreements, such as:

  * insurance companies
  * insurance brokers or agents 
  * administrators, and 
  * service providers

We maintain written contracts with third parties to help ensure that the personal information collected and/or stored about our customers is used for identified and specified purposes relating directly to legitimate business purposes.

Also, in the event that CONEXIS or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information may be one of the transferred assets. We may also release personally identifiable information when we believe that the release of such information is required by law or is necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of CONEXIS or others.

### Access and Amendment of Your Records

You have the right to access and amend your records. You may exercise this right by sending to us a written request to access and/or amend your records.

### Security

CONEXIS adheres to the generally accepted standards of security for the purpose of protecting information provided by visitors to this website. We use Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) encryption to protect sensitive information online. The servers that store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment in a locked room. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to this information. Employees are trained and certified annually on security and privacy practices.

### Linked Sites

For your convenience, this website contains links to other websites that may be of interest to you. However, you should be aware that CONEXIS has no control over these linked sites and is not responsible for the privacy policies and content of these sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites may not conform to the privacy policy maintained by CONEXIS or any other privacy statement. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website you visit.

### Children’s Privacy Protection

This website is not designed for or intentionally targeted at children 13 years of age or younger. CONEXIS collects information regarding children 13 years of age or younger only when that information is provided by, or with the consent of, their parents or guardians.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website. Please review this page periodically for changes. Your use of the Site constitutes acceptance of the provisions of this Privacy Policy and your continued usage after changes are posted constitutes acceptance of each revised policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, or any revised policy, please exit the Site immediately.

### Use of Electronic Mail (Email)

We may provide email links on our Site to further facilitate communication between CONEXIS and you. Information collected through electronic mail may be shared with our customer service department, employees, or other third parties that perform services on our behalf. Unless otherwise noted, electronic mail on our Site is not a completely secure and confidential means of communication. Non-encrypted electronic communications may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users without your knowledge and permission while in transit to us.

### Accuracy

We believe the information provided on this Site is accurate and we make every effort to minimize errors. However, we cannot absolutely guarantee the accuracy of the information provided. If you find an error, or any inaccuracy, please inform us as soon as possible.

### Contacting CONEXIS

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this website, you may contact **[support@conexis.com](mailto:support@conexis.com)** or our Compliance Officer at **[complianceofficer@conexis.com](mailto:complianceofficer@conexis.com)** or by phone at **877.CONEXIS**
